<resources>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="app_name">ChatKit</string>
    <string name="sample_title">ChatKit for Android</string>

    <string name="now_time_range">just now</string>

    <string name="duration_minutes_shortest">%1$d minute ago</string>
    <string name="duration_hours_shortest">%1$d hour ago</string>
    <string name="duration_days_shortest">%1$d day ago</string>
    <string name="duration_week_shortest">%1$d week ago</string>

    <string name="view">View</string>

    <string name="hint_enter_a_message">Type a message…</string>
    <string name="on_log_click_message">Your custom long click handler</string>
    <string name="action_delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="action_copy">Copy</string>
    <string name="copied_message">Message copied!</string>

    <string name="isOnline">Online</string>
    <string name="network_error">network error</string>
    <string name="permission_denied_error">permission denied</string>
    <string name="internet_connection_failed">no internet connection</string>
    <string name="loading">loading</string>
    <string name="deleting_message">deleting message</string>
    <string name="deleting_conversation">Deleting Conversation</string>


    <string name="error_general">Something went wrong.</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_file_type">Incorrect file type</string>
    <string name="error_bigger_file">File size is bigger than 10Mb</string>
    <string name="permissions_not_granted">Cancelling, required permissions are not granted</string>
    <string name="error_fail_load_image">Fail to load image</string>
    <string name="error_fail_crop_image">Fail to crop image</string>
    <string name="error_smaller_image">Image is too small. Required image size 100x100 px</string>
    <string name="button_ok">ok</string>
    <string name="custom_empty_text">List Empty</string>
    <string name="custom_offline_text">Oops… No Internet connection</string>
    <string name="conversations">Conversations</string>
    <string name="action_cancel">Cancel</string>

    <string name="lipsum">With the aim of helping the community, we are providing free and useful resources, information, tips and tricks to learn Android development. We believe that education is a basic human right and hence we seek to make it possible for all people in the world to learn Android development without any hassle. This is one stop solution for both android developers and learners. Here at Android Tutorial Point we thrive to deliver the best tutorials. In this direction, we are trying to create a community that will cater to your needs, whether you are a beginner or a seasoned veteran. Learners can refer our basic tutorials and developers can refer Material Design, Networking and Intermediate tutorials. Stick with us for a while, and we promise you will become an Android Rockstar.Wanna part of this journey? Contact Us. You are most cordially invited to connect with us. Kapil Gupta: Kapil is a technology enthusiast with a wide knowledge base and experience with multiple programming languages. He is currently working with world’s second largest software company. He loves to create and automate stuff. He is fond of working on new and emerging technology. Due to his love for sharing knowledge, he is a part of android tutorial point team. Feel free to contact him on Facebook or LinkedIn. You can also mail him at [email protected] Navneet Goel: Navneet is a Digital Marketing and Coding enthusiast with the heart of an entrepreneur. Passed out of NSIT Delhi in 2014, He is currently working in a multinational company as an RnD Engineer and used to write Android Tutorials in free time. He believes in giving back to society and hence started this blog. You are most welcome to connect with him on Facebook, Twitter or LinkedIn. You can also mail him at [email protected] Android Logo - In 2007, the green Android logo was designed for Google by graphic designer Irina Blok. The design team was tasked with a project to create a universally identifiable icon with the specific inclusion of a robot in the final design. After numerous design developments based on science-fiction and space movies, the team eventually sought inspiration from the human symbol on restroom doors and modified the figure into a robot shape. As Android is open-sourced, it was agreed that the logo should be likewise, and since its launch the green logo has been reinterpreted into countless variations on the original design. Linux kernel - Android variant of the Linux kernel has further architectural changes that are implemented by Google outside the typical Linux kernel development cycle, such as the inclusion of components like Binder, ashmem, pmem, logger, wakelocks, and different out-of-memory handling.</string>

</resources>
